<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Choir on The Young KL Singers</title>
    <link>https://youngklsingers.com/tags/choir/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Choir on The Young KL Singers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youngklsingers.com/tags/choir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Director&#39;s Notes: Interview with Ian</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</guid>
      <description>For “YKLS ROCKS!” director Ian Chow, this will be his fourth performance outing with the community choir, ever since he first mustered enough courage to pick up the phone to book a slot for auditions back in 2002.
Since then, Chow has produced or been on the advisory committee for almost all YKLS productions, and even stage-managed a few.
Some productions which have stood the test of time for Chow include “Through the Barricade” (2004), performing excerpts from Les Misérables and Miss Saigon musicals; “Beat It, Sing It” (also 2004) a high energy performance singing ethnic music with a 3-piece percussion backing; and “Together As One” (2010), which had YKLS members from different walks of life singing songs from different faiths and religions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Choir, Live Longer!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/join-choir-live-longer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 21:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/join-choir-live-longer/</guid>
      <description>Well, at least that&amp;rsquo;s true for a group of people participating in a choir in a Connecticut town, as found in the results of a joint study by Harvard and Yale Universities (2008). If that&amp;rsquo;s not enough to convince you, this article from CMUSE gives you a few more reasons to join choral singing.*Strengthen feeling of togetherness . In today&amp;rsquo;s increasingly &amp;ldquo;me first&amp;rdquo; society, it is nice to find a tribe to belong to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illusion &amp; Illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</guid>
      <description>We are excited and very pleased to announce that YKLS have been invited by Petronas to perform part of our Illuminations programme at the launch of the &amp;lsquo;Illusion&amp;rsquo; exhibition at Petrosains on Thursday 10th Sept!
&amp;lsquo;Illusion - Nothing Is As It Seems&amp;rsquo; exhibition, developed by Dublin Science Museum is a part art, part science retrospective of specially created works which explores the phenomenon of the seen and unseen world in our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 58th Independence Day!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 13:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! The long weekend is coming! And with that, another year of independence! As with most Malaysians, the Young KL Singers will also be taking a break to celebrate Merdeka! So while we&amp;rsquo;re normally known for singing in public, we won&amp;rsquo;t have a performance this weekend - our next public performance would be to bring you some Christmas cheer!
And so, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how the Young KL Singers is a part of Malaysia (except that we aren&amp;rsquo;t 58 years old)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 04:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations/</guid>
      <description>If a picture is a thousand words, music is a thousand pictures. Each rise and fall, every silence in between is a feeling, an image, a memory.
Now if you closed your eyes, would music be different?
Would the colours burn brighter, clearer than ever?
Join us this 6-9 August as we go on a search for answers. Guided by an exquisite repertoire of music, we will be creating an atmosphere that will truly heighten the auditory senses and unleash your imagination!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>