<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Yklsdtb on The Young KL Singers</title>
    <link>https://youngklsingers.com/tags/yklsdtb/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Yklsdtb on The Young KL Singers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:34:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youngklsingers.com/tags/yklsdtb/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2016: YKLS Does The Bard</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2016-ykls-does-the-bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2016-ykls-does-the-bard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Raw and uncut, live and unplugged&amp;rdquo; are the modern translation of how William Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s plays were staged more than 400 years ago before his passing. Despite his tragic death at 52, the legacy of the Bard of Avon lives on and continues to inspire artists and musicians alike to interpret his works in various ways.
This November, the Young KL Singers brings to you a programme of music set to the poetry and text of William Shakespeare, performed in an intimate cabaret setting for a heartfelt celebration with the audience the love of music and literature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Does The Bard</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-does-the-bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 23:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-does-the-bard/</guid>
      <description>This year, the Young KL Singers joined the arts and literary world in paying tribute to William Shakespeare, as part of a global celebration of his life and works 400 years after his death. A special collaborative project between YKLS and The Actors Studio, &amp;ldquo;YKLS Does The Bard&amp;rdquo; was held from 3rd to 6th Nov 2016 at Pentas 2, KLPAC. In a very intimate and contemporary cabaret-style setting, we presented 15 choral settings of Shakespearean text which explored the universal themes of life, love and loss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>