<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on The Young KL Singers</title>
    <link>https://youngklsingers.com/tags/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on The Young KL Singers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youngklsingers.com/tags/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Director&#39;s Notes: Interview with Ian</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</guid>
      <description>For “YKLS ROCKS!” director Ian Chow, this will be his fourth performance outing with the community choir, ever since he first mustered enough courage to pick up the phone to book a slot for auditions back in 2002.
Since then, Chow has produced or been on the advisory committee for almost all YKLS productions, and even stage-managed a few.
Some productions which have stood the test of time for Chow include “Through the Barricade” (2004), performing excerpts from Les Misérables and Miss Saigon musicals; “Beat It, Sing It” (also 2004) a high energy performance singing ethnic music with a 3-piece percussion backing; and “Together As One” (2010), which had YKLS members from different walks of life singing songs from different faiths and religions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illusion &amp; Illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</guid>
      <description>We are excited and very pleased to announce that YKLS have been invited by Petronas to perform part of our Illuminations programme at the launch of the &amp;lsquo;Illusion&amp;rsquo; exhibition at Petrosains on Thursday 10th Sept!
&amp;lsquo;Illusion - Nothing Is As It Seems&amp;rsquo; exhibition, developed by Dublin Science Museum is a part art, part science retrospective of specially created works which explores the phenomenon of the seen and unseen world in our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 58th Independence Day!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 13:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! The long weekend is coming! And with that, another year of independence! As with most Malaysians, the Young KL Singers will also be taking a break to celebrate Merdeka! So while we&amp;rsquo;re normally known for singing in public, we won&amp;rsquo;t have a performance this weekend - our next public performance would be to bring you some Christmas cheer!
And so, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how the Young KL Singers is a part of Malaysia (except that we aren&amp;rsquo;t 58 years old)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rehearsals Are Back Again!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/rehearsals-are-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 12:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/rehearsals-are-back-again/</guid>
      <description>And we&amp;rsquo;re back after a short break!
Rehearsals are starting again tonight, along with auditions for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s interested! Even though Illuminations is over, we still have a surprise in store for you before the end of this year as we bring you some more choral lovin&amp;rsquo;!
For current (and old) members, this means you don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait until next year to get your choir kicks again, and for those interested in singing and performing with the YKLS, this is a chance for you to join in the fun without having to wait until next year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Perks Of Being In YKLS</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/4-perks-of-being-in-ykls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/4-perks-of-being-in-ykls/</guid>
      <description>Originally this was going to be titled &amp;lsquo;8 Perks of Being in YKLS&amp;rsquo; but half of them seem to be pretty much what you expect from joining a choir, and you didn&amp;rsquo;t come here to read about obvious advantages, right?
You did? Oh. Okay, then.
 You learn singing techniques to up your game. You pick up loads of new songs and choral arrangements. You experience what it is to be part of a production, from rehearsals to bumping in at the venue to tech runs until the end of the performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interpretations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/interpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 13:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/interpretations/</guid>
      <description>Music can be a lot of things to different people: it can remind you of something, somewhere or someone, it can elicit emotions.
The sense of adventure and epic saga to expect when you hear the main theme to Star Wars or The Legend of Zelda. The dread when you hear the theme from Jaws. The feeling of awe and terror from Karl Jenkin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Dies Irae&amp;rsquo; from his Requiem. The spiralling feeling of despair when Lux Aeterna from Requiem For A Dream starts to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Tips to Not Losing Your Voice!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/10-tips-to-not-losing-your-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/10-tips-to-not-losing-your-voice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.youngklsingers.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ariellosesvoice-300x167.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ariellosesvoice&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, if you’ve watched the Little Mermaid, you know that Ariel took forever to get together with Prince Erik because Ursula cast a spell (!) and stole Ariel’s voice.
At YKLS, we learn fast – drawing from Ariel’s harrowing experience, we are very careful in making sure we don’t lose our voices, especially when concert’s only 2 weeks away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And because we believe everybody can and should sing, whether or not you wish to marry a handsome prince, we would like to share with you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YKLS’ 10 Personal Tips to Not Losing Your Voice!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>