<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://youngklsingers.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://youngklsingers.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Director&#39;s Notes: Interview with Ian</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:11:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/directors-notes-interview-with-ian/</guid>
      <description>For “YKLS ROCKS!” director Ian Chow, this will be his fourth performance outing with the community choir, ever since he first mustered enough courage to pick up the phone to book a slot for auditions back in 2002.
Since then, Chow has produced or been on the advisory committee for almost all YKLS productions, and even stage-managed a few.
Some productions which have stood the test of time for Chow include “Through the Barricade” (2004), performing excerpts from Les Misérables and Miss Saigon musicals; “Beat It, Sing It” (also 2004) a high energy performance singing ethnic music with a 3-piece percussion backing; and “Together As One” (2010), which had YKLS members from different walks of life singing songs from different faiths and religions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2017: YKLS Rocks!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2017-ykls-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 19:06:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2017-ykls-rocks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From the 60&amp;rsquo;s to the new millennium, from classic rock to hard rock to alternative to fusion rock (among many others), The Young KL Singers (YKLS) will be pouring their hearts out to celebrate their 15th Anniversary with the production, YKLS Rocks!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That&#39;s it. Period.</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/thats-it.-period./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2017 12:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/thats-it.-period./</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s Friday, folks! Let&amp;rsquo;s help you hurry in the weekend with a bit of random stuff about one of the YKLS productions (ok admittedly we were going through some old videos and hey let&amp;rsquo;s choose this).
YKLS Period! In 2013!*After being with Young Choral Academy (and assistant music director for the YKLS) for yonks, this was the year Tracy headed off to Toronto in August to do her Masters, and bring a taste of cili padi to the Canadians.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Rocks!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-rocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 16:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-rocks/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Choir, Live Longer!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/join-choir-live-longer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 21:38:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/join-choir-live-longer/</guid>
      <description>Well, at least that&amp;rsquo;s true for a group of people participating in a choir in a Connecticut town, as found in the results of a joint study by Harvard and Yale Universities (2008). If that&amp;rsquo;s not enough to convince you, this article from CMUSE gives you a few more reasons to join choral singing.*Strengthen feeling of togetherness . In today&amp;rsquo;s increasingly &amp;ldquo;me first&amp;rdquo; society, it is nice to find a tribe to belong to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2016: YKLS Does The Bard</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2016-ykls-does-the-bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Nov 2016 17:34:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2016-ykls-does-the-bard/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Raw and uncut, live and unplugged&amp;rdquo; are the modern translation of how William Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s plays were staged more than 400 years ago before his passing. Despite his tragic death at 52, the legacy of the Bard of Avon lives on and continues to inspire artists and musicians alike to interpret his works in various ways.
This November, the Young KL Singers brings to you a programme of music set to the poetry and text of William Shakespeare, performed in an intimate cabaret setting for a heartfelt celebration with the audience the love of music and literature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Does The Bard</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-does-the-bard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2016 23:04:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-does-the-bard/</guid>
      <description>This year, the Young KL Singers joined the arts and literary world in paying tribute to William Shakespeare, as part of a global celebration of his life and works 400 years after his death. A special collaborative project between YKLS and The Actors Studio, &amp;ldquo;YKLS Does The Bard&amp;rdquo; was held from 3rd to 6th Nov 2016 at Pentas 2, KLPAC. In a very intimate and contemporary cabaret-style setting, we presented 15 choral settings of Shakespearean text which explored the universal themes of life, love and loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Christmas Countdown: 1 Day</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-1-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2015 05:17:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-1-day/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s one more day to the show! We&amp;rsquo;ve got an exciting line-up and fine-tuning it in preparation for tomorrow!
And you&amp;rsquo;ll have the opportunity to take a bit of time off from Christmas shopping with the masses (unless you&amp;rsquo;ve already completed your Christmas shopping, which then we&amp;rsquo;ll say, &amp;ldquo;Well done, you!&amp;rdquo;), come to Ruang, relax and be entertained, have a bite to eat and mingle, then when you&amp;rsquo;re fully recharged, head back to continue your Christmas shopping!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Christmas Countdown: 3 Days</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-3-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2015 13:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-3-days/</guid>
      <description>The weekend is looming closer and it&amp;rsquo;ll soon be time to celebrate Christmas Around the World with us!
Today let&amp;rsquo;s introduce you to the members who&amp;rsquo;ll be spreading the Christmas cheer!
Catch us this Sunday at Ruang Subang Jaya at 3pm!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Christmas Countdown: 4 Days</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-4-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2015 13:35:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-4-days/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s four more days to the show!
So here&amp;rsquo;s four random facts about YKLS and choir in general.1. Four, Squared There are four main vocal parts in a choir: soprano, alto, tenor and bass.
There was one time when even the four parts were further split into 4 parts each: Soprano 1a, Soprano 1b, Soprano 2a, Soprano 2b, Alto 1a, Alto 1b, Alto 2a, Alto 2b, Tenor 1a, Tenor 1b, Tenor 2a, Tenor 2b, Bass 1a, Bass 1b, Bass 2a and Bass 2b!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>YKLS Christmas Countdown: 5 Days</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-5-days/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2015 05:00:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/ykls-christmas-countdown-5-days/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s five more days until Christmas Around The World! And while waiting for the weekend, let&amp;rsquo;s have a little guessing game about the production!
As the name implies, YKLS will be bringing you nativity songs from around the world and not just the usual Christmas carols we&amp;rsquo;re all used to. Just as with our last Christmas production (The YKLS Christmas Project), the songs may not necessarily be in English - we introduced a few other carols in French, Spanish and even in English that&amp;rsquo;s not commonly heard here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Carolling, YKLS Style</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/christmas-carolling-ykls-style/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 12:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/christmas-carolling-ykls-style/</guid>
      <description>After every production, there&amp;rsquo;s always that lull near the end of the year where members get restless because there are no more rehearsals, no more singing and no more meeting up until next year. And so to help alleviate choir withdrawal symptoms, sometimes there&amp;rsquo;s the post-production viewing party and carolling rehearsals.
Carolling!

That is, if we&amp;rsquo;re lucky and have been approached for a gig and if we get enough members to participate - after all, carolling gigs tend to be held near Christmas when everyone will have their own celebrations and holidays.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2015: Christmas Around the World</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2015-christmas-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 11:42:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2015-christmas-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>From the mystical forests of North America to the seaside towns of Spain; from white winters in Korea to sunny summers in Australia&amp;hellip;
Join the Young KL Singers as we take you on a musical Yuletide journey round the world!
Bring your family and friends along for an afternoon of beautiful songs, scrumptious food and wonderful company. We&amp;rsquo;ve even planned a little surprise just for you!****
RUANG Event Space
Concert Time: 13 December 2015: 3pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Christmas Around the World</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/christmas-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 23:59:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/christmas-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>Come celebrate Christmas with the Young KL Singers!
Enjoy high tea at Ruang Event Space at Subang while we entertain you with carols from all over the world. It&amp;rsquo;s a one day event only, so don&amp;rsquo;t miss out!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The YKLS Christmas Project</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/the-ykls-christmas-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2015 13:51:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/the-ykls-christmas-project/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s November! And with it, another eight more Fridays until Christmas!
And six more Sundays until the upcoming YKLS Christmas production! This will be the second Christmas production that the Young KL Singers will be performing (well, third, if taking into account Scrooge The Musical in 2005).
In the earlier years YKLS would have 2 productions in a year, and there were also carolling gigs at the year end as well (hey, check out the YKLS milestones!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live On Stage, Live This Wednesday!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/live-on-stage-live-this-wednesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2015 13:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/live-on-stage-live-this-wednesday/</guid>
      <description>Live on Stage is on this Wednesday!
Feel free to drop by in the afternoon at Young Choral Academy and be entertained by the performances by YKLS members! This is the one time where you get to see the members let their hair down and perform their favourites!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illusion &amp; Illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Sep 2015 13:05:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illusion--illuminations/</guid>
      <description>We are excited and very pleased to announce that YKLS have been invited by Petronas to perform part of our Illuminations programme at the launch of the &amp;lsquo;Illusion&amp;rsquo; exhibition at Petrosains on Thursday 10th Sept!
&amp;lsquo;Illusion - Nothing Is As It Seems&amp;rsquo; exhibition, developed by Dublin Science Museum is a part art, part science retrospective of specially created works which explores the phenomenon of the seen and unseen world in our eyes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy 58th Independence Day!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Aug 2015 13:38:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/happy-58th-independence-day/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! The long weekend is coming! And with that, another year of independence! As with most Malaysians, the Young KL Singers will also be taking a break to celebrate Merdeka! So while we&amp;rsquo;re normally known for singing in public, we won&amp;rsquo;t have a performance this weekend - our next public performance would be to bring you some Christmas cheer!
And so, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at how the Young KL Singers is a part of Malaysia (except that we aren&amp;rsquo;t 58 years old)!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rehearsals Are Back Again!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/rehearsals-are-back-again/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2015 12:25:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/rehearsals-are-back-again/</guid>
      <description>And we&amp;rsquo;re back after a short break!
Rehearsals are starting again tonight, along with auditions for anyone who&amp;rsquo;s interested! Even though Illuminations is over, we still have a surprise in store for you before the end of this year as we bring you some more choral lovin&amp;rsquo;!
For current (and old) members, this means you don&amp;rsquo;t have to wait until next year to get your choir kicks again, and for those interested in singing and performing with the YKLS, this is a chance for you to join in the fun without having to wait until next year!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Auditions!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/auditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 18:32:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/auditions/</guid>
      <description>Want to be part of the Young KL Singers? We&amp;rsquo;re open for auditions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live On Stage!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/live-on-stage/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2015 13:48:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/live-on-stage/</guid>
      <description>Live on Stage is coming! This is an event where members of the Young KL Singers can finally showcase their own thing, whether it be a solo piece, a boy band / girl group / mixed team song, however you want it. As most of the year would be spent preparing for the production this is a time where members can actually perform anything they like, in costume too!
A piece of trivia: &amp;gt;Live on Stage concept actually originated from a small scale Valentine production that we did back in 2003 entitled &amp;ldquo;Love Is In The Air&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illuminations: Lights Out</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations-lights-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Aug 2015 18:44:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations-lights-out/</guid>
      <description>And it&amp;rsquo;s a wrap for Illuminations!
It&amp;rsquo;s been a great journey for every one of us, and we would like to thank all of you who could make it to experience the show. Thank you for your support!
To the Dignity children and the members from the Malaysian Association of the Blind, we&amp;rsquo;re glad to have shared this experience with you with us and we hope we have managed to entertain you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Star Write Up!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/the-star-write-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Aug 2015 14:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/the-star-write-up/</guid>
      <description>The online version of The Star&amp;rsquo;s write-up on Illuminations is now available! With more photos!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illuminations Is Sold Out!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations-is-sold-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 18:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations-is-sold-out/</guid>
      <description>Illuminations opens today! It&amp;rsquo;s a very exciting time and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to bring the show to you tonight!
Best news yet is that we&amp;rsquo;re sold out!
 OK we realise that this may not be good news to those have to buy tickets. We&amp;rsquo;re sorry, guys, really. We would really love to have you join in the experience!
To everyone coming, we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One More Day To Illuminations!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/one-more-day-to-illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2015 09:19:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/one-more-day-to-illuminations/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s one more day until Illuminations opens! It&amp;rsquo;s an exciting time as we polish up the performance for your entertainment! And while we&amp;rsquo;re not polishing up our act, we&amp;rsquo;re polishing up our meals.

Because this year there are helpful members offering to food for others - so everyone meets downstairs at KLPAC to mooch on nasi lemak ayam / sotong, KFC and dim sum!

The Young KL Singers. Big on singing, big on eating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Perks Of Being In YKLS</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/4-perks-of-being-in-ykls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 06:16:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/4-perks-of-being-in-ykls/</guid>
      <description>Originally this was going to be titled &amp;lsquo;8 Perks of Being in YKLS&amp;rsquo; but half of them seem to be pretty much what you expect from joining a choir, and you didn&amp;rsquo;t come here to read about obvious advantages, right?
You did? Oh. Okay, then.
 You learn singing techniques to up your game. You pick up loads of new songs and choral arrangements. You experience what it is to be part of a production, from rehearsals to bumping in at the venue to tech runs until the end of the performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BFM Interview With The Music Director!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/bfm-interview-with-the-music-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 17:00:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/bfm-interview-with-the-music-director/</guid>
      <description>Illuminating With Songs, Singing to Make Clearer: BFM interviews our music director Chi Hoe on what to expect for Illuminations!
You can listen to the interview at BFM&amp;rsquo;s website here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R&amp;R à la Mode YKLS</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/rr-%C3%A0-la-mode-ykls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 12:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/rr-%C3%A0-la-mode-ykls/</guid>
      <description>If you feel that things have been getting a tad hectic, or your workload have you feeling stressed out, or you&amp;rsquo;re bummed out by goings-on around you, then it&amp;rsquo;s time for a little R&amp;amp;R.
That&amp;rsquo;s right, some Respite &amp;amp; Rhythms. For proper Rest &amp;amp; Relax we are sure you may have better ideas, but if you have only a couple of hours and need to get away from all the craziness going on in the world around you for a little while, we would like to invite you to come join us instead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Behind The Scenes, Day 1: Laundry Day</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/behind-the-scenes-day-1-laundry-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 13:55:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/behind-the-scenes-day-1-laundry-day/</guid>
      <description>And so yesterday the YKLS stepped into Indicine to start setting up the venue for Illuminations! While it may be a concert in the dark, it&amp;rsquo;s not as straightforward as just turning off all the lights (what would happen to our matinee concert, then?). Indicine, as with some of the studios in KLPAC, have glass sliding doors so that everyone can appreciate the great outdoors in the comfort of the cool indoors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inside Intimate Indicine!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/inside-intimate-indicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 04:25:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/inside-intimate-indicine/</guid>
      <description>8 more days until Illuminations, and we&amp;rsquo;ll be moving rehearsals to Indicine at KLPAC where we will be performing in! There&amp;rsquo;s much to be excited about!
Given the nature of the concert, Indicine presents an appropriate venue because it&amp;rsquo;s smaller and cosier (so you won&amp;rsquo;t have to strain to hear us from the back row!) and we can keep you all in the dark (literally&amp;hellip;and for now figuratively as well). There&amp;rsquo;s still plenty to do, from preparing the venue to be pitch dark, to testing the sound in the new space, making adjustments and going for dim sum dinner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milestones</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/milestones/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 03:56:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/milestones/</guid>
      <description>2011
November YKLS staged Together As One, a groundbreaking concert production incorporating the music of various faiths and religions at both The Actors Studio at Lot 10 and at the Penang Performing Arts Centre.
2010
November YKLS, YCA Youth Chamber Choir and the Malaysian Institute of Art choir collaborated on a mini-concert, , which showcased the talents of Malaysian composers and arrangers.
July YKLS participated in the 6th World Choir Games in Shaoxing, China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interpretations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/interpretations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jul 2015 13:53:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/interpretations/</guid>
      <description>Music can be a lot of things to different people: it can remind you of something, somewhere or someone, it can elicit emotions.
The sense of adventure and epic saga to expect when you hear the main theme to Star Wars or The Legend of Zelda. The dread when you hear the theme from Jaws. The feeling of awe and terror from Karl Jenkin&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;Dies Irae&amp;rsquo; from his Requiem. The spiralling feeling of despair when Lux Aeterna from Requiem For A Dream starts to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2014: Incantations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2014-incantations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2014-incantations/</guid>
      <description>INCANTATIONS explores choral music inspired by ancient rituals and traditions. From rainsongs, war chants, spells to thunderstorms, join us as we pit the fragility of the human existence against the universe : powerful, alluring, and shrouded in mystery.Video 1: Teaser Video: Incantations 2014!Video 2: Music Director Introduces IncantationsVideo 3: What&amp;rsquo;s Exciting About Singing in a Choir? Video 4: The Stories in our Songs
BFM Podcast: Interview with Producer and Music Director!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illumination Teasers!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illumination-teasers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 13:53:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illumination-teasers/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been putting out a couple of quick teasers on social media so far ( Facebook page! Instagram!), here&amp;rsquo;s another one on what to expect!
Given the theme of our concert, you should plug in a pair of earphones and listen to this with your eyes closed for best effect!
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XtPuUk90_bw
You can also follow us on Instagram (@youngklsingers) for more teasers (like the one below)!
https://instagram.com/p/5dkNpik12A/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concerts</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 17:57:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concerts/</guid>
      <description>2016: YKLS Does The Bard
&amp;ldquo;Raw and uncut, live and unplugged&amp;rdquo; are the modern translation of how William Shakespeare&amp;rsquo;s plays were staged more than 400 years ago before his passing. Despite his tragic death at 52, the legacy of the Bard of Avon lives on and continues to inspire artists and musicians alike to interpret his works in various ways.
This November, the Young KL Singers brings to you a programme of music set to the poetry and text of William Shakespeare, performed in an intimate cabaret setting for a heartfelt celebration with the audience the love of music and literature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 04:19:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/illuminations/</guid>
      <description>If a picture is a thousand words, music is a thousand pictures. Each rise and fall, every silence in between is a feeling, an image, a memory.
Now if you closed your eyes, would music be different?
Would the colours burn brighter, clearer than ever?
Join us this 6-9 August as we go on a search for answers. Guided by an exquisite repertoire of music, we will be creating an atmosphere that will truly heighten the auditory senses and unleash your imagination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daily Seni Online Shout Out!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/daily-seni-online-shout-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 03:57:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/daily-seni-online-shout-out/</guid>
      <description>Daily Seni Online has done a nice write-up for our upcoming concert, Illuminations! You can read it here!
Tickets are selling fast! You can get more information here!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block Your Dates! YKLS Will Be Illuminating KL This 6th - 9th August!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/block-your-dates-ykls-will-be-illuminating-kl-this-6th---9th-august/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 03:46:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/block-your-dates-ykls-will-be-illuminating-kl-this-6th---9th-august/</guid>
      <description>Check our Facebook eventfor all the info!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sing Different</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/sing-different/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 03:43:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/sing-different/</guid>
      <description>If there&amp;rsquo;s one thing about the Young KL Singers, it&amp;rsquo;s that there&amp;rsquo;s always something new every year - whether it be singalongs from musicals, breaking it down with jazz pieces, celebrating our musical and cultural heritage and even choral music inspired by traditions and rituals all over the world, it&amp;rsquo;s certain that the Young KL Singers are an adventurous bunch to tackle different genres.
This year though, the Young KL Singers are going to be doing something totally different from the previous years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concert 2015: Illuminations</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2015-illuminations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 20:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/concert-2015-illuminations/</guid>
      <description>If a picture is a thousand words, music is a thousand pictures. Each rise and fall, each silence in beween is a feeling, an image, a memory.
Now if you close your eyes, would the music be different?
Would the colours burn brighter, clearer than ever?
Join us this 6th - 9th August as we go on a search for answers. Guided by an exquisite repertoire of music, we will be creating an atmosphere that will truly heighten the auditory senses and unleash your imagination!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Audition Season Is Over, But...</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/audition-season-is-over-but.../</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Apr 2015 20:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/audition-season-is-over-but.../</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve been plotting and scheming, and we think you&amp;rsquo;re going to like what we have cooking! What we can share for now, though, is our new Facebook page! Start following us to get updates, or really just to get your dose of sillies: The Young KL Singers on Facebook</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;re Open for Auditions!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/were-open-for-auditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jan 2015 01:56:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/were-open-for-auditions/</guid>
      <description>WHY JOIN US?
&amp;ldquo;I joined for the harmony but also experienced comedy, drama and possibly some therapy!&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Meeting like minded people who enjoyed making beautiful music together - it became like a safe haven for me. I formed life-long friendships and we had many wonderful experiences I will never forget.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I went into YKLS but never came back out. Not because I was lost, it&amp;rsquo;s because I have found &amp;ldquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Penang, We&#39;re Coming For You!!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/penang-were-coming-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2014 17:01:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/penang-were-coming-for-you/</guid>
      <description>We can&amp;rsquo;t thank everybody enough for the amazing KL run of Incantations!
We certainly did not expect 3&amp;frasl;4 full-house shows, and it was especially great to have performed to the (slightly scared :P) children from PPR Pantai, elderly residents of the Rumah Kebajikan Ci Hang-Chempaka and choir singers from the National Council of the Blind at the Charity Matinee.
So it&amp;rsquo;s Penang this 7-9 Nov, and we promise you it&amp;rsquo;ll be nothing less awesome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15% Off Cat in the Box Coffees!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/15-off-cat-in-the-box-coffees/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2014 11:52:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/15-off-cat-in-the-box-coffees/</guid>
      <description>Get 15% off any one coffee at the Cat in the Box Cafe with each ticket to YKLS Incantations@DPAC! Just show your ticket, stub or booking ref no. between now and 9 November to claim.
Find them at Lot 111 Heritage Lane, Empire Damansara or www.catintheboxcafe.com. And might we also say - congratulations to our feline friends at Cat in the Box on the launch of their new pad at Empire Damansara.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incantations: The Stories In Our Songs</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/incantations-the-stories-in-our-songs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2014 22:45:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/incantations-the-stories-in-our-songs/</guid>
      <description>Speaking of mermaids&amp;hellip;did you know that Ulek Mayang is about a battle to save a fisherman from having surrendered his soul to a beautiful sea princess?
Every song we will sing in Incantations has a beautiful tale behind it. In this video, the choir gives you a little glimpse at what these stories are. To feel the full magic, come join us October 16-19 @ DPAC. Enjoy the video!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Tips to Not Losing Your Voice!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/10-tips-to-not-losing-your-voice/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2014 18:37:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/10-tips-to-not-losing-your-voice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://www.youngklsingers.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/10/ariellosesvoice-300x167.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;ariellosesvoice&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, if you’ve watched the Little Mermaid, you know that Ariel took forever to get together with Prince Erik because Ursula cast a spell (!) and stole Ariel’s voice.
At YKLS, we learn fast – drawing from Ariel’s harrowing experience, we are very careful in making sure we don’t lose our voices, especially when concert’s only 2 weeks away!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And because we believe everybody can and should sing, whether or not you wish to marry a handsome prince, we would like to share with you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;YKLS’ 10 Personal Tips to Not Losing Your Voice!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why We Love Choir: A Feisty Soprano Explains!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/why-we-love-choir-a-feisty-soprano-explains/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 20:43:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/why-we-love-choir-a-feisty-soprano-explains/</guid>
      <description>Why do we love singing in a choir? Alia tells you in this video one of the billion reasons why!
 And then we leave it to Linus to articulately capture all the other reasons:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s Incantations About? Our Music Director Speaks!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/whats-incantations-about-our-music-director-speaks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2014 11:53:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/whats-incantations-about-our-music-director-speaks/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;You will be mesmerised&amp;hellip; Enthralled&amp;hellip; You will be drawn into this world that we will be creating for you.&amp;rdquo;
Introducing the ever-passionate Music Director - Chi Hoe!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Incantations @ penangpac, Penang</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/incantations--penangpac-penang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2014 19:48:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/incantations--penangpac-penang/</guid>
      <description>7 Nov 2014, FRI, 8:30PM | RM20 (Preview Night)
8 Nov 14, SAT, 3:00PM | RM35* 8 Nov 14, SAT, 8:30PM | RM35* 9 Nov 14, SUN, 3:00PM | RM35* *RM25 Students, Disabled, TAS Card Members
* GET TICKETS*
Online:
 Tel: +604-899 1722 / 2722
What&amp;rsquo;s Incantations about? Click here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sponsorship</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/sponsorship/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 05:24:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/sponsorship/</guid>
      <description>Help us continue to keep choral music affordable and accessible in Malaysia! YKLS needs sponsorship for two main reasons:(1) Cover production costs, such as equipment and production space rental.
(2) Fund tickets for underprivileged groups to attend the Charity Matinee show. Every year , YKLS dedicates our Saturday afternoon show to the underprivileged as our way of sharing the joy of music with those who have less then we do. Past organisations have included Rumah Hope, Rumah Impian, Malaysian Association of the Blind, Magic, Agathian Shelter Home, RACTAR, NASOM, and Dignity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join Us!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/join-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2014 04:22:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/join-us/</guid>
      <description>Ever wanted to be part of a choir?
Interested in singing and performing, whether just within the choir or on stage to an audience?
Concerned that you may need a musical background, or that it&amp;rsquo;ll be hard work?
Mark your calendars! The Young KL Singers will be having auditions soon!
[caption id=&amp;ldquo;attachment_3089&amp;rdquo; align=&amp;ldquo;aligncenter&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;700&amp;rdquo;]  Join us![/caption]
As a community choir, the Young KL Singers welcomes everyone to join in the fun - no music knowledge required beforehand (you&amp;rsquo;ll learn as you go along), you get to perform in various places, you meet all sorts of people with the same passion, and while it will be hard work when you prepare for a performance (hey, good things never come easy) when it&amp;rsquo;s over you&amp;rsquo;ll find that it was worth the effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/contact-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 22:10:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/contact-us/</guid>
      <description>Young Choral Academy (TTDI) 114A, Jalan Burhanuddin Helmi Taman Tun Dr. Ismail 60000 Kuala Lumpur.
Tel: +603-7733 4691
Email: youngchoral@gmail.com
Web: www.youngchoral.my
 The Young KL Singers
Email: info@youngklsingers.com
Web: www.youngklsingers.com Follow us on Twitter and Instagram @youngklsingers Subscribe to us on Youtube @youngklsingers
Got questions?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Past Concerts</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/past-concerts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 21:00:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/past-concerts/</guid>
      <description>2015: YKLS Does The Bard
This year, the Young KL Singers joined the arts and literary world in paying tribute to William Shakespeare, as part of a global celebration of his life and works 400 years after his death. A special collaborative project between YKLS and The Actors Studio, “YKLS Does The Bard” was held from 3rd to 6th Nov 2016 at Pentas 2, KLPAC. In a very intimate and contemporary cabaret-style setting, we presented 15 choral settings of Shakespearean text which explored the universal themes of life, love and loss.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 20:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/media/</guid>
      <description>https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLwC0tDqJNAlUilVNPNpHzDRu-8IMBElqG
https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLwC0tDqJNAlWpGwny2KoHQEyAhEk_YLZU</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buy Tickets</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/buy-tickets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 20:54:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/buy-tickets/</guid>
      <description>KL Performing Arts Centre Pentas 2
Concert time: 31 Aug - 2 Sep @ 8.30pm 2 Sep - 3 Sep @ 3pm
Tickets prices: Adult: RM 50 Disabled, TAS Card Members, Seniors &amp;amp; Kids: RM 40
Tickets available: KLPac Box Office: +603 4046 9000 TicketPro Box Office: +603 7880 7999 TicketPro Online: http://www.ticketpro.com.my/concert/2159335-klpac-YKLS-Rocks.html</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About The Choir</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/about-the-choir/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2014 20:49:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/about-the-choir/</guid>
      <description>The Young KL Singers (YKLS) is a bunch of people with a few things in common:
(1) We love singing!
(2) We see humour in everything.
(3) Every Monday, Wednesday and Friday night, we spend about two and a half hours or more perfecting our craft.
&amp;hellip;But it&amp;rsquo;s all totally worth it.
So what are you really?
Very simply, YKLS is a community choir. We’ve got teachers, consultants, central bankers, flight attendants, piano accompanists, voice healers, business owners, interior designers, mothers, students, yoga instructors, traders, pharmacists, et cetera – all of whom feel life would not be complete without spending three nights a week singing, harmonising and having fun doing it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sneak Peek: Incantations 2014!</title>
      <link>https://youngklsingers.com/sneak-peek-incantations-2014/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2014 19:41:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://youngklsingers.com/sneak-peek-incantations-2014/</guid>
      <description>Hello everyone! Here&amp;rsquo;s a glimpse at what YKLS&amp;rsquo;s got in store for you at our concert this October (KL) and November (Penang). This is possibly the most adventurous music we&amp;rsquo;ve ever done and we are so, so excited!
For more info on the concert, tickets and showtimes, check out the links on the left column.
 </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>